

Email auroraking0112@gmail.com Chicago, Illinois, United States Address

+1 978 393 1620 Phone Date of birth Jun 10, 1997 Nationality American

#### **SUMMARY**

I have been actively working in software development since 2015. Experienced with a variety of technologies and languages, I have a solid understanding of all aspects of full-stack development. Through I drive to understand the bigger picture behind problems, I develop unique, wellthought-out solutions.

#### EXPERIENCE

Oct 2020 - Nov 2022

#### Senior Full Stack Developer

Freelancer

- Developed an application that manages subscriptions and monthly payments.
- Developed an event management web application where the client can manage his events and all of the guests.
- Created a custom CMS with Vue.js and AWS Lambda for a client with special needs in functionality.
- Transferred an existing in-house system to the AWS Cloud by utilizing specialized AWS solutions HTML, CSS to increase performance and reduce cost.
- Designed and developed an application through which users are able to generate questionnaires.
- Developed a children sponsorships platform coupled with a management system.

Jun 2017 - Dec 2017

#### React Developer

Freelancer

- Created a reusable UI framework based on MUI.
- Used Apollo Client to work with the GraphQL API.
- Reduced a ton of boilerplate codes with custom

Technologies: Apollo, Jest, TypeScript, React, Code Review, APIs, UI, REST APIs, JSON Web Tokens (JWT), JSX

Jul 2019 - Mar 2020

#### Vue.js Developer

Consumer Internet Labs LLC

- Made tags and user recommendation systems based on similar user preferences.
- Built a scalable, maintainable, and clean architecture.
- Optimized the back-end performance by changing the database structure and rewriting heavy SQL queries.

Technologies: Bulma, REST APIs, PostgreSQL, Django, React, Full-stack, Full-stack Development, SQL, Linux,

Feb 2018 - Mar 2019

#### Full Stack Developer

404 Publishing

- Developed speed improvements for calculations on a distributed network of Node.js instances, which communicate with each other and rely on each other's data.
- Configured and implemented an audio streaming service to stream a radio show on a Next.js page.
- Extended the functionality of the front end and increased stability and loading times.

Technologies: Next.js, React, MongoDB, JavaScript, PHP, APIs, IntelliJ

#### EDUCATION

University in London, Ontario, Canada

Jun 2013 - Mar 2017

### Bachelor's Degree in Computer Science

Western University

### KEY SKILLS

- Team Leader
- Self-Motivating
- Try to succeed

### LANGUAGES

English

Advanced. Diploma in Advanced English

Chinese

**Native** 

# MY SKILL SETS

# Languages Expertise:

PHP, JavaScript, JQuery, Ajax, Web Services, Vue/Vuex/Vue-router, React/Redux-Saga, React-Hook, RESTful API, XML, HTML5, AMP pages, Python.

### Frameworks Expertise:

React(Redux, Next.js), Vue.js(Vuetify, Nuxt.js), Laravel, Node/Express CodeIgniter, Bootstrap, AngularJS, Android SDK, .NET, Svelte

### **Database Expertise:**

MySQL, MongoDB, Database Management, Amazon S3, SQL Server, Oracle SQL

## 3rd party APIs Expertise:

jQuery, Paypal, Stripe, Quick Books Payments, AWS Web Services, Google Maps, Google Maps API, Google API, Facebook API, Twitter API

### Platforms Expertise:

Wordpress, Stripe, LAMP, Linux, Ubuntu, Windows

### **Tools Expertise:**

Figma, Adobe Suite, Notepad++, GitHub Management, Pivotal Tracker, Basecamp, Google Analytics, Trello, Jira

### PAST WORKS

- -https://wedo.lu/ (Laravel/Vue)
- -https://nexthuman.me (React/firebase)
- -http://examgenie.com/#/
- -https://infermedica.com/
- -https://pinpoint.promo/ (PHP/Laravel)
- -https://www.johnfowlerholidays.com/ (React/Node)
- -http://vgcakes.co.uk/ (CakePhp)
- -http://examgenie.com/#/ (Angular)
- -http://ashleyrosedesigns.net/ (woocommerce)
- -https://spicysubscriptions.com/ (Shopify) -https://www.optimallyorganic.com/ ( Magento)
- -https://southwickstorage.co.uk/ (Wordpress)